http://www.promodel.com/privacy/

Process Simulator Autodesk Edition
Download Process Simulator Evaluation (Free)
Process Simulator Autodesk Edition
Download Process Simulator Evaluation (Free)
Last updated January 3, 2020
This Policy explains how personal information collected about our business prospects and customers on ProModel owned websites, herein referred to as "Sites" (e.g. www.promodel.com, futureflowrx.com), in ProModel developed products, herein referred to as "Products" (e.g. ProModel, MedModel, Enterprise Portfolio Simulator, Process Simulator, FutureFlow Rx, Shipyard AI), from incoming email inquiries, from conferences / tradeshows, telephone calls or other valid means is used and disclosed by ProModel and its subsidiaries and affiliated companies ("ProModel" or "We").This Policy does not apply to websites, applications, or services that display or link to different privacy statements.
This policy was most recently updated based on CCPA to include a specific contact path below for California residents to inform ProModel Corporation that they are requesting a change in how ProModel handles their personal information.
HOW WE COLLECT PERSONAL DATA
We collect information you provide us such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, fax number, company name, credit card payment information and demographics. We may also obtain information from other sources and combine that with information we collect. When you visit our Sites, some information is automatically collected. This may include information such as the Operating System (OS) running on your device, Internet Protocol (IP) address, access times, browser type, and language, and the website you visited before our Sites. We also collect information about how you use ProModel's Sites and Products. We automatically collect information using "cookies" and Web beacons. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website and web beacons are electronic images that may be used on our Sites or in our emails. Among other things, cookies help us improve our Sites, our marketing activities, and your experience. We use cookies to see which areas and features are popular and to count visits to our Sites.
Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Sites. ProModel does not respond to "Do Not Track" browser signals or other mechanisms. Third parties may collect personal information about your online activities over time and across sites when you visit the Sites or use the ProModel products.
HOW WE STORE AND USE THE PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED We use the data to provide helpful information and improve the user experience with ProModel Corporation as well as to maintain, protect and improve our current products and to develop new ones. We use personal data collected through our Sites and Products as described in this Policy or on our Sites. For example, we may use your information to:
Improve our services, Sites, Products and how we operate our business; Understand and enhance your experience using our Sites, Products and services; Provide and deliver Products and services you request; Respond to your comments or questions and for our team to provide service; Send you related information, including confirmations, invoices, technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages; Communicate with you about promotions, training, upcoming events and news about products and services offered by ProModel and our selected partners; Link or combine it with other information we get from third parties, to help understand your needs and provide you with better service; and Protect, investigate and deter against fraudulent, unauthorized or illegal activity.
ProModel may store and process personal data in the United States and other countries. We store data on secure ProModel servers as well as with GDPR compliant third party data processors including Salesforce.com and Mixpanel. SHARING OF PERSONAL DATA Information You Share Our privacy policy does not cover any third party services. To learn about those third parties' privacy practices, please visit their policies.
Service Processor
Service Provided
Type of Data
Website
Google
Analytics / search
Anonymous metadata
privacy.google.com/businesses/compliance/
Information We Share
We do not share your personal information with third parties without your consent other than:
With third parties who work on our behalf provided such third parties enter into a written agreement with ProModel requiring that the third party provide at least the same level of privacy protection as ProModel; With privacy GDPR compliant third party data processors including Salesforce.com and Mixpanel. To comply with laws or to respond to lawful requests and legal process (provided that ProModel will endeavor to notify you if ProModel has received a lawful request for your information); To protect the rights and property of ProModel, our agents, customers and others including to enforce our agreements, policies and terms of use; In an emergency, including to protect the personal safety of any person; and For the purposes of a business deal (or negotiation of a business deal) involving sale or transfer of all or a part of our business or assets (business deals may include, for example, any merger, financing, acquisition, divestiture or bankruptcy transaction or proceeding).
We may also share aggregate or de-identified / pseudonymous or anonymous data derived from your personal data. Personal Information Security ProModel takes reasonable steps to help protect your personal information in an effort to prevent loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. It is your responsibility to protect your usernames and passwords to help prevent anyone from accessing or abusing your accounts and services. You should not use or reuse the same passwords you use with other accounts as your password for our services. CHILDREN If you are under 18, or the age of majority in the jurisdiction in which you reside, you may only use the ProModel website, Products and services with the consent of your parent or legal guardian. YOUR INFORMATION CHOICES AND CHANGES
You may opt out of receiving promotional emails from ProModel by following the instructions in those emails. If you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your ProModel projects or our ongoing business relationship. You may also send requests about your contact preferences, data accuracy, data processing/usage or data deletion by visitng our GDPR Information Request page or our CCPA Information Request page . Individuals who have provided information to ProModel's customers must send requests to change or delete such information to the particular ProModel customer. DATE RETENTION / DELETION AND YOUR RIGHT TO BE FORGOTTEN
ProModel retains your data while you are an active prospective customer or a customer. If you become an inactive prospective customer we may delete some or all of your information even if you do not request it. If you are or have ever been a customer we will delete your information upon your request. If you do not request it we will retain your information so that we may provide you the best possible support should you contact us again in the future.
CONSENT TO USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA By using ProModel’s website, filling out forms, Opting-In and using our products and services you consent to the usage of your personal data as stated in this policy. In addition you have the rights to control that same data as stated in this policy via ProModel’s Tech Support Team. CHANGES TO THIS POLICY ProModel may change this Policy from time to time. If we make any changes to this Policy, we will change the "Last Updated" date above. You agree that your continued use of our Services after such changes have been published to our Services will constitute your acceptance of such revised Policy. CONTACTING PROMODEL AND DISPUTE RESOLUTION ProModel commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. Inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact ProModel at:
ProModel GDPR Information Request
ProModel CCPA Information Request
Postal mail: ProModel Corporation, 7540 Windsor Dr., Suite 300, Allentown, PA 18195
QUESTIONS If you have any questions about this Policy, please contact us at support@promodel.com.
Technology-Enabled Predictive Analytics.
Download Process Simulator Evaluation (Free)
Site Map
Solutions:
Industries:
Services:
Consulting
Custom Development
Technical Support
Training
Products:
Download Process Simulator Evaluation (Free)
ProModel
ProModel Autodesk Edition
Shipyard AI
Resources:
About Us:
This website uses cookies to improve your user experience. If you continue on this website, you will be providing your consent to our use of cookies.
Accept
More info
